http://www.cambridgefx.com/legal/#legalSection4

Cambridge Link
Need login credentials?Become a client.
Cambridge Link
Need login credentials?
Become a client.
Legal and Licensing
Your trust is one of our most valued assets. To that end, we are committed to providing you with the most secure environment possible in which to do business with us.
Terms of Website Use
The information contained in this website is provided for informational purposes only and does not constitute financial, investment, tax, legal or other professional advice and should not be relied on as such.
Although we use our best efforts to provide accurate information, Cambridge does not make any representation or give any warranty in respect of this website or its contents. In particular, and without limiting the generality of the foregoing, Cambridge does not represent, warrant or guarantee the accuracy, currency, reliability or completeness of the information contained in this website; that the website will be available without interruption, error or omission; that defects will be corrected; or that the website and the servers that make it available are free from viruses or harmful components.
This website may contain links to websites controlled or offered by third parties. Cambridge disclaims any and all liability for any information, materials, products or services posted or offered on or at any such linked sites.
This website and its contents are provided “as is” and “as is available,” without any warranties, representations or conditions of any kind, either express or implied, including, without limitation, warranties as to merchantability, fitness or non-infringement of intellectual property. Cambridge shall not be responsible in any manner, and expressly disclaims all liability for, any direct, indirect, special or consequential damages, however caused, arising out of the use of this website or any website(s) to which it is linked, the information contained herein or in respect to decisions made or actions taken in reliance on the information in this website.
Privacy and Cookie Policies
At Cambridge, our top priority is protecting the privacy of our clients and potential clients. We do not sell the personal data/information that we collect from such persons.
Cambridge’s Privacy Policy reflect applicable law, which varies by location. For further details, please refer to the Privacy Notices below. These documents are also available, on request, in formats more accessible for persons with disabilities; please send these requests to privacy@fleetcor.com.
Canadian Privacy and Cookie Policy: Click here to view and download the policy.
Australian Privacy and Cookie Policy: Click here to view and download the policy.
European Privacy and Cookie Policy: Click here to view and download the policy. This European Notice applies to:
1. The worldwide processing of personal data about individuals located in the European Union and/or the UK (even after the expected completion of Brexit).
2. Personal data processed by one or both of Cambridge’s UK entities (Cambridge Mercantile Corp. (UK) Limited & Cambridge Mercantile Risk Management (UK) Ltd), regardless of the individual data subject’s location.
US Privacy and Cookie Policy: Our US policy is comprised of two documents which are to be read together.
1. The main policy document on FLEETCOR Technologies Inc.’s website, here (Cambridge is a FLEETCOR (NYSE: FLT) company).
2. This supplementary document focused primarily on consumer financial privacy protections offered by the US federal statute GLBA (The Gramm-Leach-Bliley Act).
For a short, simple overview of what cookies are, and how to control them, please download this info sheet.
Accessible Customer Service Policy
Cambridge’s Commitment to Accessibility
Cambridge Global Payments (“Cambridge”) is committed to providing a barrier-free environment for our clients, employees and other stakeholders: whether they enter our premises, receive services from us or access our information.
Cambridge strives to meet the needs of its employees and customers with disabilities and is working hard to remove and prevent barriers to accessibility.
Our business is committed to fulfilling our requirements under the Ontario statute: Accessibility for Ontarians with Disabilities Act (“AODA”).
As an organization, we are committed to treating all people in a way that allows them to maintain their dignity and independence. Cambridge believes in integration and equal opportunity, is committed to meeting the needs of people with disabilities in a timely manner, and is committed to meeting the accessibility requirements under the AODA.
To read our Accessible Customer Service Policy, download it here.
Please click here to view our Self-Certified Report from 2013, and click here to view the 2017 report.
Multi-Year Accessibility Plan
Our Multi-Year Accessibility Plan will be made available upon request. To request a copy, please contact us.
Contacts
If you would like to request information regarding our accessibility or are having trouble accessing our services, please contact:
Human Resources
Phone: (416) 646-6401
Licensing and Regulatory Information
Cambridge is extremely diligent in its practice of maintaining the appropriate licensing and regulatory standards for a Money Services Business in all of the regions in which we operate. Please use the link below to download this information for all of our legal entities.
Download PDF
Security Guidelines for Online Activity
Security guidelines
Security guidelines for a safe and secure online experience
TLS 1.2 protocol
Transport Layer Security (TLS) is the protocol used on the internet to encrypt end-to-end connections. If you are using an outdated web browser or your browser is not configured to use TLS 1.2, upgrading your browser to the latest version or changing the settings of your web browser to only allow TLS 1.2 is recommended.
Protect your credentials
To protect user accounts, ensure that a unique user id and password is assigned to each user and ensure that complex and long password is utilized. Also passwords are confidential and should never be shared with anyone. In case you feel that your password has been compromised, change your passwords promptly. Do not share same password on multiple systems, as compromise of credential from one of the systems can be leveraged to access other systems.
Multifactor Authentication
Utilize multi-factory and 2-step verification to protect user accounts from unauthorized access to ensure protection even if your password was stolen.
Cambridge has designed its application to utilize a 2-step verification to protect user accounts from unauthorized access if someone manages to obtain your password. An additional layer of security requires a One Time Password (OTP) to be entered along with your username and password.
OTP and the 2-step verification can be delivered by DUO app on your smartphone, SMS message with a PIN number and Phone call to a land line. The administrator can choose any of the 3 options during initial setup.
Visit only trusted websites
Always verify and ensure correctness of the web page’s URL before entering any personal data such as your user id and password. Ensure the website has HTTPS certificate by clicking on the lock symbol at the top or bottom of the browser window.
Use a recent browser
Using a recent browser is the best way to avoid common attacks and keep your account safe. Cambridge strongly recommends that you update your browsers regularly to ensure you have access to the latest security standards provided by the vendor. You should also update all the plugins (e.g. Java, Flash) that are integrated within the browser.
Phishing & social engineering
What is phishing?Phishing is an attempt to acquire sensitive information such as usernames, passwords, credit card details etc. often for malicious reasons, by pretending to be a trustworthy entity in a mail. It is the most common way to do social engineering. In practice it often involves asking you to click on a link to a malicious website that looks like the site of a trusted institution. Phishing can also be performed via phone or chat by people pretending to be a trusted party, such as the helpdesk.
Secure mailing practices
Use work-related emails only for official purposes
Never send confidential information by email unless it is encrypted
Always check that you are sending an email to the correct person
Read and comply with the Email Policy within your organisation
Protect your email password as emails are often used to verify password resets in some applications
How to Detect a phishing attempt?
It’s usually Unexpected/unsolicited
Contains spelling mistakes
It may lack personal information
It usually requires the recipient to undertake an action such as open attachment, click on a link to access a website, provide information or process a transaction.
How to prevent a phishing attempt?
Always verify the sender’s email address
Do not open any attachment or click on a link whose sender you are unsure of
Do not disclose confidential information to anyone via any webpage or a form
Confirm links embedded in emails by placing your mouse-over the link to see the real URL
Mobile computing
Some helpful security tips while using a mobile device is as follows;
Never leave unattended in a public place or vehicle
Keep locked away when not in use
No confidential information should be stored on corporate mobile devices
Use screen lock and if possible whole disk encryption
Do not install unauthorized software
Do not allow others to use your corporate device
File a Complaint
Our goal is to achieve the highest standard of excellence in customer service as well as in payment processing; so let us know if you have any feedback, complaints, concerns and/or questions. To help us resolve your issue or accurately direct your comments, please make sure to include a full summary of the situation, names of any Cambridge employees that were involved, and suggestions for possible solutions. All information you provide will be used in accordance with Cambridge’s Privacy Policy.
Please submit your feedback to CustomerServices@cambridgefx.com.
If you have a complaint or concern pertaining to licensing and/or regulatory issues, you will find a schedule below with a list of complaint agencies by state (US only), and their contact information. That said, we strongly encourage you to first contact Cambridge with your complaint, so we can rectify your problem more quickly.
Download the PDF here.
ALASKA
For Alaska Residents Only:
If your issue is unresolved by Cambridge Mercantile Corp. (U.S.A.) at (212) 594-2200, please submit formal complaints with the State of Alaska, Division of Banking & Securities.
Formal complaints must be in writing, please download the form here:  https://www.commerce.alaska.gov/web/portals/3/pub/DBSGeneralComplaintFormupdated.pdf
Formal complaint forms may be submitted via:
1. Fax:  907-465-1230
2. Email:  msb_licensing@alaska.gov
3. Mail:  Division of Banking & Securities PO Box 110807 Juneau, AK  99811-0807
If you have questions regarding formal complaints, please call 907-465-2521.
CALIFORNIA
If you are a California resident and if you have complaints with respect to any aspect of the money transmission activities conducted at this location, you may contact the California Department of Business Oversight at its toll-free telephone number, 1-866-275-2677, by email at consumer.services@dbo.ca.gov, or by mail at the Department of Business Oversight, Consumer Services, 1515 K Street, Suite 200, Sacramento, CA 95814.
COLORADO
If you are a Colorado Resident and have a Complaint about the money transmitter – the company that sent your money – ALL complaints must be submitted in writing. Please fill out the Complaint Form provided on the Colorado Division of Banking’s website and return it and any documentation supporting the complaint via mail or email to the Division of Banking at: Colorado Division of Banking, 1560 Broadway, Suite 975, Denver, CO 80202, email: DORA_BankingWebsite@state.co.us, website: www.dora.colorado.gov/dob. Download the M07 Customer Notice here.
Si usted es un residente del estado de Colorado y tiene una queja sobre el agente de envíos monetarios – la compañía que envió su dinero – todas las quejas deben de ser entregadas por escrito. Por favor llene la forma de quejas que se encuentra en el sitio web de la División Bancaria de Colorado y entregue la forma junto con los documentos que apoyen su queja por correo o por correo electrónico a la División Bancaria de Colorado al: Colorado Division of Banking, 1560 Broadway, Suite 975, Denver, CO 80202, email: DORA_BankingWebsite@state.co.us, website: www.dora.colorado.gov/dob. Descargue el aviso del cliente M07 aquí.
Download PDF
Annual Modern Slavery and Human Trafficking Statement
This document is also available, on request, in formats more accessible for persons with disabilities; please send these requests to legal@cambridgefx.com
Download PDF
Social Engineering: Fraud Awareness
We take our role seriously in ensuring that both we, and our customers, can confidently operate efficiently and securely. Download our information sheet to learn more about how to detect and prevent fraud.
Download PDF
Terms and Conditions for Cambridge Accounts
Click below to read and download the terms and conditions applied to Cambridge Global Payments Accounts for all of our customers globally.
. All Rights Reserved.
Copyright ©2020. All Rights Reserved.
Cambridge is part of FLEETCOR a leading global business payments company.
×
×
Stay Informed
Gain insights into trends and developments in global currency markets with our breaking market wires and research reports.
Enjoy practical foreign exchange and global payment solutions customized to meet your unique business needs.
